[
  {
    "id": 11,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "Write the keyword used to declare a constant variable.",
    "answer": "const"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What method is used to convert a JSON string into a JavaScript object?",
    "answer": "JSON.parse"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What keyword is used to declare a block-scoped variable?",
    "answer": " "
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What value does a function return if it doesnâ€™t explicitly return anything?",
    "answer": "undefined"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "Which operator is used to check both value and type equality?",
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What will this code output?\n\nconsole.log(typeof NaN === 'number');",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What method converts a JavaScript object into a JSON string?",
    "answer": "JSON.stringify"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What keyword is used to handle errors in a try block?",
    "answer": "catch"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What keyword is used to define an asynchronous function?",
    "answer": "async"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "type": "input",
    "question": "What function is used to schedule code execution after a delay?",
    "answer": "setTimeout"
  }
]
